<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android Basics</string>
    <string name="array_title">Things To Know</string>
    <string name="notes">Explanation</string>
    <string-array name="titles_array">
        <item>TextView</item>
        <item>Image View</item>
        <item>Layout: ConstraintLayout</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="exp_array">
        <item>A TextView is a widget used to display text in an Android application.
            Its one of the most commonly used UI elements in Android apps for displaying
            labels, messages, instructions, etc.TextView can be customized in terms of
            text size, color, font style, alignment, and more.</item>
        <item>An ImageView is a widget used to display images in an Android application.
Its used when you want to show images such as icons, photos, logos, etc., in your apps UI.
ImageView can load images from various sources like drawable resources, assets, URLs, etc.
It supports various scale types (e.g., centerCrop, fitXY, fitCenter)
            to control how the image is displayed within the ImageView bounds.
Like TextView, ImageView is also a subclass of the View class and can be
            added to layout XML files or created dynamically in code.</item>
        <item>ConstraintLayout is a flexible layout manager in
            Android used to create complex and responsive UI designs.
It allows you to create layouts by positioning and aligning views relative
            to each other or relative to the parent layout.
Views within a ConstraintLayout are connected or constrained to each other using constraints.
Constraints define the position, size, and alignment of views within the layout.
ConstraintLayout is preferred over other layouts like RelativeLayout or
            LinearLayout for its flexibility, performance, and ease of creating responsive UIs.
Its part of the AndroidX library and supports features like chains, guidelines,
            barriers, and more for advanced layout designs.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>